♪I wrote a stroke♪
♪About you and me♪
♪You pass like the wind♪
♪I follow like a leaf♪
♪But just you and me♪
♪Had no happy ending♪
♪Perhaps it was just a chance encounter♪
♪I turn memories over with great care♪
♪Afraid to lose the past♪
♪Tears fall quietly with the plot♪
♪Shattered with no response♪
♪The wind once♪
♪Through layers of mist♪
♪And snowy scenes♪
♪Gently cradled the leaf in my palm♪
♪But♪
♪Winds will cease♪
♪Leaves will wither♪
♪Our meeting was too fleeting♪
♪It's an unavoidable fate♪
♪I too once♪
♪Walked through♪
♪A sea of people♪
♪Unafraid of how far it is♪
♪Racing under stars toward you♪
♪But♪
♪Time is heartless♪
♪You never yield♪
♪Let love remain♪
=Spring Night=
=Episode 24=
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
(in the court, ending
his pursuit of power with blood.)
(Jin Chuan ascended the throne,)
(rehabilitated
the wronged minister Shen Jinyuan)
(and reopened the imperial exam.)
(The land is well governed,)
(with people living in contentment.)
(One year later)
That's it.
This special imperial exam.
Proceed according to this plan.
Yes.
Anything else?
I've heard
people say in Your Majesty's study
hangs a divorce paper.
Seeing it for the first time today,
I found it rather novel.
What do they
say about it?
They all speak of
Your Majesty's incognito story
with Miss Shen.
Some bold opera troupes
have even adapted it into operas.
And the ending of these operas?
Is it reunion?
Or separation?
These operas have no ending.
Because everyone feels
Your Majesty and Miss Shen's story
hasn't ended yet.
(Divorce Paper)
(Fortune Teller Liu)
When the Emperor
was still the Crown Prince,
he killed the traitor and cleared
(Guanyin Temple)
the loyal.
Especially when suppressing
the rebellion,
he was valiant and skilled,
unmatched by anyone!
Was he truly that formidable?
Of course!
After that,
the imperial exam became fair,
no more favoritism based on region.
We finally have a chance to rise.
(No candied hawthorn
in the world gets wet)
Mai Tian.
♪Lanterns glow as night has just begun♪
♪Spring rain greets dreams♪
♪Cutting fragment branches♪
♪That girl in your heart♪
♪Round fans veil her crimson grace♪
♪Warming plum wine for guests to taste♪
♪In this tender world♪
♪I strum the strings and sing aloud♪
♪Drunk, I gaze upon my sword♪
♪Falling petals drift
with fragrant streams♪
It's been a long time.
Have you been well?
Quite well.
And you?
Not well.
Not well at all.
I've missed you terribly.
Where have you been
all this time?
♪Spring rain greets dreams♪
Are you asking me as the Emperor?
Or as Ye Wuming?
♪Round fans veil her crimson grace♪
♪Warming plum wine for guests to taste♪
♪In this tender world♪
♪I strum the strings and sing aloud♪
♪Drunk, I gaze upon my sword♪
♪Falling petals drift
with fragrant streams♪
♪Simmering red beans♪
♪All my longing's fully cooked♪
♪My love endures♪
Ye Wuming.
♪In this tender world♪
♪Mountains and rivers
shine in your eyes♪
♪White horse in autumn wind♪
♪Blossoms in the south,
a mere fleeting dream♪
♪One spoonful of moonlight♪
♪Two streams of silent tears
slip into dreams♪
♪Stars and galaxies♪
♪Time stretches long since your goodbye♪
(Guanyin Temple)
(Buddha)
Are you nervous?
No.
I am a little nervous.
Why?
What if the outcome is bad?
What then?
How could that be?
It won't happen.
Of course.
Usually, pretty girls
like me
are lucky, you know?
Don't worry.
Even if the fortune says something bad,
I will defy fate and change it for you.
Promise?
Pinky swear.
Seal it.
- Do it.
Your Majesty.
How about we
skip the fortune-telling part?
You just defy fate directly?
That won't do.
I always insist on
proper justification.
If the result is naturally good,
why defy fate
to change it?
Your Majesty.
I...
This is feudal superstition.
It... it's fake!
Deceitful!
- Do it.
I have
long stopped swindling people.
My main business now is storytelling,
cross-talk, and Xihе drum singing.
Divined the Emperor's fate.
(Divined the Emperor's Fate)
Your Majesty.
This is
just a marketing tactic.
You shouldn't take it seriously.
I don't care.
Anyway, we're here now.
You have to do my reading.
Do it.
A hostile line crosses your palm.
Signifying a poor, lonely youth.
Your fortune will come
only after your husband's demise.
Your Majesty.
(Palmistry Guide)
Not my fault.
That's exactly what the book says.
Alright, let's not give him a hard time.
May your business prosper.
Let's go.
Take care, Your Majesty.
So
the book actually has it recorded.
Oh, right.
Ye Wuming.
You're so talented with words.
Could you
write a book for me?
Write a book for you?
Of course I can.
What kind of book?
- Well...
- The Domineering Prince?
Oh, stop it!
Of course, it should be our story!
Just make it
about this thick.
A book this thick?
Won't my eyes get sore reading it?
Sore eyes would be even better.
I'll read it to you.
You'll read it to me?
Then I'll want to hear it once, twice,
three times...
many times.
You finish writing it first.
A cockroach!
♪The wind drifts alone and free♪
♪Through seasons, none asks of me♪
♪Spring fades, and autumn wails♪
♪Only the waning moon
lights my solitude♪
♪Love arose with the wind's sigh♪
♪On a cold night,
a swan's shadow flashes by♪
♪You're deeply devoted♪
♪Yet spring wind betrayed your heart♪
♪I miss you so much♪
♪I never forget you♪
♪A brief period of love-sickness♪
♪You won my heart over♪
♪Why did we first meet♪
♪Seeking spring's song
and night whispers♪
♪Long autumn comes,
and wild geese southward fly♪
♪The azure clouds know my name♪
♪I remember you, and you understand me♪
♪Watching the sun set♪
♪Autumn departs, and beauty fades away♪
♪To lean on you once more someday♪